/* jshint esversion: 11 */

const quizData = [{
    question: "A Full Stack developer should be able to write front-end code in which of the following?",
    a: "Java",
    b: "Javascript",
    c: "HTML",
    d: "All of the above",
    ans: "choice4"
}, {
    question: "Which of the following are front end technologies?",
    a: "JQuery",
    b: "SASS",
    c: "AngularJS",
    d: "All of the above",
    ans: "choice4"
}, {
    question: "Which of the following are popular databases?",
    a: "MySQL",
    b: "Oracle",
    c: "MongoDB",
    d: "All of the above",
    ans: "choice4"
}, {
    question: "Why do we use JQuery?",
    a: "Creation of mobile Application",
    b: "Creation of Interactive website",
    c: "Database connectivity",
    d: "None of the above",
    ans: "choice2"
}, {
    question: "A Full Stack developer works on which of the following ?",
    a: "Mobile Application Development",
    b: "Web Development",
    c: "Database Technologies",
    d: "All of the above",
    ans: "choice4"
}, {
    question: "Which of the following JavaScript cannot do?" ,
    a: "JavaScript can react to events" ,
    b: "JavaScript can manipulate HTML elements" ,
    c: "JavaScript can be use to validate data" ,
    d: "All of the Above" ,
    ans: "choice4"
}, {
    question: "What keyword is used to declare variables in javascript" ,
    a: "Var" ,
    b: "Dim" ,
    c: "String" ,
    d: "None of the above" ,
    ans: "choice1"
}, {
    question: "The attribute used to define a new namespace is." ,
    a: "XMLNS" ,
    b: "XmlNameSpace" ,
    c: "Xmlns" ,
    d: "XmlNs" ,
    ans: "choice3"
}, {
    question: "When a JavaScript object is sent to Java, the runtime engine creates a Java wrapper of type" ,
    a: "ScriptObject" ,
    b: "JSObject" ,
    c: "JavaObject" ,
    d: "Jobject" ,
    ans: "choice2"
}, {
    question: "How can you make a list that lists the items with numbers?" ,
    a: "<ul>" ,
    b: "<list>" ,
    c: "<ol>" ,
    d: "<dl>" ,
    ans: "choice3"
}];